Let's sign up to our website
using a browser extension named "MetaMask"
Choose a password that you will use
to access MetaMask
Usually your browser will remember this
password for you
Here you can see a "seed phrase":
12 english words
Please, write them on a piece of paper
and don't show to anybody
It's your "password", in case you'll lose
your access to MetaMask
or you'll want to use the same
"public key" on your smarphone/tablet
Confirm some of the words
you've written down
At the top you can see the first and
the last chars of your "public key"
Go back to our website,
then click on "refresh page"
Connect the wallet to this page
In the field "Message" you can see this
website address and a random number
Click on "Sign"
This green text is equal to your MetaMask
"public key"
From now on you can log in
with MetaMask
and your progress (and some settings)
will be saved
That's all
Have fun! :-)