How to install MetaMask
on smartphone/tablet?
Open "Play Store"
or "App Store" if you have an iPhone/iPad
In the search bar look for
"MetaMask"
Install it
then open it
Click on "Get started"
In this guide we select "Import..."
because we want to have
the same public address like
on computer, right? :)
Type in your secret phrase,
that you've received
installing MetaMask on computer
You can select "Enable..."
No tour, thanks
Now you can see tha same public key
like the one on your computer
Click on "Browser"
Then in the address field
type in our website's address:
www.god-s-world.net
Click on "Enter",
then "Sign up with MetaMask"
"Connect"
"Sign"
Now, at the bottom of the page
you can see the first and the last chars
of your public key
The same you can see at the top
From now on your progress will be saved
Congratulations!
Have fun!